insidegameofwar.com 2019-03-18

# Privacy Policy - Inside Game of War

This page gives information on the privacy policy used by Park House Solutions Ltd and protects any information that you give Park House Solutions Ltd  when you use this website. Park House Solutions Ltd  is committed to ensuring that your privacy is treated with the utmost protection. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

### Collection

You can browse InsideGameOfWar.com without telling us who you are. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information to our servers. We may collect other information that is provided to us by your web browser. This may include the browser you used to come to our website, the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) of the website that you just visited before visiting our website, which pages on our website you visit, any search terms you entered, which URL you go to next, and your Internet Protocol (IP) address.

We may collect and store the following personal information:

Transactional information based on your activities  
Community discussions and correspondence sent to us;  
Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from InsideGameofWar.com, cookies information;  
Other information, including IP address and standard weblog information, and supplemental information from third parties.

You can choose not to provide information to us, but in general some information about you is required in order for you to register as a member; purchase products or services; complete a profile;ask us a question; or initiate other transactions on our site. If you use a message board, blog, or chat room on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there may be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

### Marketing

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent.

### Use

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a customized experience that is safe, smooth, and efficient. You agree that we may use your personal information to:

Provide the services and customer support you request;  
Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities;  
Enforce our User Agreement, other agreements and policies;  
Customize, measure, and improve our services and the Site’s content and layout;  
Protect our rights, property, and safety, including that of our employees, users, or others;  
Tell you about or provide targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; and  
Compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties.

### Our Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose personal information to comply with legal requests, subpoenas, court orders (or substantially similar legal procedures), enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or if we believe it is necessary to protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please contact contact@insidegameofwar.com
